<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Nofe Green</title>
    <link>https://nofegreen.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Nofe Green</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 08:40:31 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nofegreen.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nofegreen.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 08:40:31 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofegreen.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Tentang Nofe Green Hi semua&amp;hellip; Nofe Green adalah sebuah Blog Tutorial dengan thema komputerisasi, dimana semua tutorial menyangkut dengan teknologi komputer. Semua tutorial yang ada di Blog Nofe Green ini telah saya pelajari dan di ujicoba secara pribadi, tapi jika masih ada kesalahan atau Bug jangan ragu untuk mengirimi saya Notice berupa email atau berkomentar di bawah artikel yang terkait.
Email &amp; Kontak : coming soon Kalau menyangkut pribadi saya, saya adalah lulusan D3 Manajemen Informatika Komputer pada perguruan tinggi swasta UMMY dan sudah tamat tahun 2015 dengan nilai Alhamdulillah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://nofegreen.github.io/pages/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 08:40:31 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofegreen.github.io/pages/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Nofe Green Health services can help you understand and manage your health data. They include HealthVault,HealthVault Insights, Nofe Green Band devices, other Nofe Green Health applications and related products. The Band helps you keep track of data like heart rate and steps taken. The Band can also use Cortana to take notes and receive notifications from your phone. The Nofe Green Health applications send data to Nofe Green servers and allow you to view, manage and control the data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>